George Rezmikov

UI/UX Designer

PHONE 8 (903) 215-21-90

E-MAIL georgeowlson@gmail.com

PORTFOLIO georges-portfolio.vercel.app

@GeorgeOwlson

<u>georgereznikov</u>

<u>georgereowlson</u>

Education

YANDEX PRACTICUM UX/UI DESIGNER

JANUARY 2021 - OCTOBER 2021

SCREAM SCHOOL
MOTION GRAPHIC DESIGN

SEPTEMBER 2019 - FEBRUARY 2019

BACHELOR OF ARTS, MGUSIT

2003 - 2008 MOSCOW, RUSSIA

Skills

FIGMA
PHOTOSHOP
ILLUSTRATOR
INDESIGN

AFTER EFFECTS

HTML/CSS/JS (BASICS)

About

My name is George. I'm a multidisciplinary designer with 8 years of experience and a particular interest in UI/UX design. Throughout my career, I have worked with big brands such as Coca-Cola, Fanta, Sprite, Nissan, HP, Adidas, McDonalds. During my time at TBWA our team was awarded two Bronze Cannes Lions in Print Outdoor и Art Direction.

Work experience

FC LOKOMOTIV MOSCOW / ART DIRECTOR

JULY 2021 - APRIL 2022

· designed visual identity and its graphic elements (social media, outdoor advertising, prints, stadium navigation)

- designed a loyalty program website (logo and identity creation, UX copywriting)
- · collaborated with a product marketing team to achieve higher results
- developed design concepts and its further scaling
- · created motion graphics for (the football club's video channel) Loko TV

TBWA MOSCOW / CREATIVE DESIGNER

APRIL 2018 - JULY 2021

- developed creative design concepts to clients (Alcon, Nissan, HP, Adidas, Gazprom)
- designed visual content: key visuals, car retouching, landing pages, websites
- · created motion design for cases and internal projects
- · created and edited Power Point/Keynote presentations for clients
- mentored and instructed interns

THE DIRECTORS / DESIGNER

APRIL 2015 - APRIL 2018

- was promoted within a six-month timeframe for exceeding goals
- · designed original graphics for 33 Fanta Mini Apps on VK.com
- ideated and produced visual content for Sprite and Semper on social media platforms
- · designed a website encyclopedia for Semper and its products
- created a special project website for Coca-Cola and designed limited edition cans for the rock/pop/hip-hop summer campaign
- · designed the layout of print collateral: brochures, flyers, banners, etc.